<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BCET</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About College</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "About BCET.\n\n"

        "Bengal College of Engineering and Technology, Durgapur was set up under the aegis of "
        "SKS Educational and Social Trust in 2001 with an objective of imparting quality education"
        "in Engineering/Technology and Management for the upliftment of the society and the masses."
        "The college offers a host of under graduate and post graduate degree courses in different"
        "branches of engineering and management. Proximity to the region’s premier educational and"
        "research institutes like NIT, Durgapur, CMERI (Central Mechanical Engineering Research "
        "Institute), IIT-Kharagpur, ISI (Indian Statistical Institute-Kolkata),Jadavpur University,"
        "Kolkata and Indian Institute of Engineering Science and Technology (IIEST), Howrah, have "
        "resulted in a vast pool of intellectual capital. Today, its infrastructure includes "
        "contemporary classrooms, well equipped labs, separate facilitated hostels for boys and "
        "girls, to name a few. Many high profile Ministers and dignitaries have visited and praised"
        "the college campus and its infrastructure.\n"
        " BCET displayed unmatched entrepreneurial talent by receiving the National Championship "
        "Award for three consecutive years in a row (2008, 2009 and 2010)and three years Runners-Up"
        "(2011, 2012 and 2013),and Regional Champions ( 2014 and 2015) which ensures a special "
        "recognition for the entire Durgapur region in the entrepreneurial map of the nation. "
        "BCET has got the coveted NBA accreditation of four of its courses and this reflects the "
        "quality of education at this institution.\n\n"

        "Recognization.\n\n"

        "AICTE Approval\n"
        "MAKAUT (Previously known as WBUT) Affiliation\n\n"

        "Faculty.\n\n"

        "Click here to faculty list "
        "http://bcetdgp.ac.in/faculty.html"\n\n"

        "Mission and Vision.\n\n"

        "VISION\n"
        "Not simply to succeed but to surpass – Vince te Ipsum (surpass oneself). Foster a vibrant "
        "learning milieu focusing on U.G., P.G., technical education and inter-disciplinary research"
        "of international standard, fulfilling social concerns and global economic demands.\n\n"

        "MISSION\n"
        "1.Nurture human talent into proactive professionals and achieve excellence through discipline"
        ", perseverance and creative thinking.\n"
        "2.Impart and disseminate knowledge through industry-institution interaction and encourage "
        "newer services for human development.\n"
        "3.Facilitate world class technical education through innovative research and development "
        "programme related to indigenous technology.\n"
        "4.Shape management and technological practices in India by creating new frontier of knowledge,"
        "developing new generation of ethical, dependable, entrepreneurial and socially sensitive "
        "technocrats and employable global citizens. \n"
        "5.To fortify the institute to turn into a trustworthy Centre for Education, Research, "
        "Development and Outreach (ERD and O).\n\n"

        "QUALITY POLICY\n"
        "“We are committed towards providing personalized quality services by understanding the "
        "students and the parents. We will also work towards continual improvement in Quality of our"
        "Services by adapting the International Quality Management System Standard ISO 9001:2008 as "
        "the minimum requirement.”"\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="large_text1">
        "I feel glad to introduce to you Bengal College of Engineering and Technology. Established "
        "in 2001 it is the Flagship College of SKS Group of Institutions. Now it stands as a premier"
        "Engineering College in West Bengal with well known reputation and with all its eligible "
        "courses accredited by National Board of Accreditation and All India Council for Technical "
        "Education (AICTE), New Delhi.\n\n"

        "To support the cause of Education, SKSgi has courses ranging from primary education to "
        "Post Graduate Technical Degrees, and campuses at strategic locations both in West Bengal "
        "and Uttar Pradesh. In Higher Education there are courses available in Engineering, "
        "Computing, Pharmaceutical Sciences, Management, and many more.\n\n"

        "The faculty in the college is one of the best in its class, and the college has a tie-up "
        "with several reputed industries in the country so as to provide an excellent on-campus "
        "placement to its graduating students.\n\n"

        "BCET is an ISO 9001:2008 certified institute and all its eligible courses are NBA "
        "Accredited and hence internationally recognised. The institute is at the verge of a very "
        "rapid growth and it is being aimed to achieve the Deemed University status in future.\n\n"

        "I convey my best wishes to all the students and their parents for a successful future and '
        "good education.\n\n"

        </string>

    <string name="large_text2">
        "Bengal College of Engineering and Technology have been able to pump gusto of certainty by "
        "remaining focused on our shared mission, values and goals. Our focus on quality learning "
        "strategies set in accordance with Washington Accord, collaboration with different reputed "
        "organizations like NIT Durgapur, CMERI, DSP, ASP, DPL, ALSTOM, PCBL, Graphite India and "
        "Indian Air Force (Panagarh Base), IITs, JU, IIEST (BESU) etc have made us a professional "
        "learning community- a community built to shift the paradigms in the domain of technological"
        "and management education nationwide. The NBA Accreditation of four courses of BCET will "
        "help us to bolster R and D Programme, resulting in wider exposures of Industry-Academia "
        "interactions and also an International recognition of the courses conducted by the College.\n\n"

        "Engineering is a creative art and it certainly needs a cohort of mentors who gets this "
        "creative art a platform. Our E-Cell, has given wings to the creative ideas fostered by our "
        "students. Some of our students have already emerged as successful entrepreneurs at national"
        "level. We salute these great techies and welcome those to our portal who want to live larger"
        "than life. It is a matter of pride that our Hon’ble Chairman Sir Shri. S. K. Sharma has "
        "recently been felicitated by the Rotary International for his landmark contribution in "
        "technical and management Education which has credited SKSgi with a benchmark at national level.\n\n"

        "Our quality and outcome based education has attracted myriad national and multinational "
        "companies to recruit our students and our placement cell stands as Prometheus to provide "
        "multiple job opportunities to our students. This, once more testifies the verity of the "
        "statement that SKSgi strives its best to launch its students in the job market with aplomb."\n\n"

        "Today, all the Institutions under SKS banner have become trend setters and torchbearers in "
        "the fields of Engineering, Management, Pharmaceutical and General Education. They are a "
        "class of their own in areas like Campus Placement, Global Education Opportunities, and "
        "Infrastructural Facilities with enviable performance in all India exams and entrepreneurship."
        "Our achievements are the products of our relentless pursuit of quality and excellence to "
        "offer more educational and moral enlightenment to our pupils.\n\n"

        "You can sit and see the world change. Or you can stand and drive the change. The choice is "
        "yours. If you are at SKSgi, we are confident that you will be the architects of your own fate."
        "We hope that your stay with us will be enjoyed and cherished forever. Knowledge based manpower "
        "is the need of the hour and we have to face the challenge through quality technical and "
        "professional education. I feel a pull at my heart at this point to mention that our Chairman"
        "of SKS Group of Institutions Shri.S.K.Sharma and our Vice-Chairman Shri Mayank Gautam have "
        "been the cascade of all our dynamic endeavors in catering valueand outcome based education "
        "to thousands of young minds. It is the patronage of our visionary management, co-operation "
        "of our worthy faculty members and the best wishes of our collaborators which has enabled us"
        "to emerge Bengal college of Engineering and Technology as a centre for excellence-a flagship"
        "college under the aegis of SKS Educational and Social Trust committed towards the motto "
        "Vince-te-Ipsum (surpass thyself). The accolades like NBA Accreditation and the attainment"
        "of OUTSTANDING ENGINEERING INSTITUTE (EAST) by ABP NEWS National Education Awards, achieved"
        "by the college in this successful journey of transforming blooming buds into techno blossoms"
        "deserve a special mention.\n\n"

        </string>

    <string name="large_text3">
        "The year 2016, and the journey of BCET goes through sixteen consecutive years-always growing"
        "in size, variety and quality in technological and management education that it imparts to "
        "it's pupil from near and far.Through these years it has come a long way from starting four "
        "courses in B.Tech in the inaugural year 2001, to successfully running nine Bachelors' and "
        "three Masters' courses in technology since 2011.The Masters' level courses in Management "
        "like MBA and MCA continue under able guidance and leadership of faculties.\n\n"

        "It is a matter of great pleasure and pride that the college is providing an excellent quality"
        "of education and mentoring for the students, aspiring to be competent professionals in "
        "technology and management. Research projects under AICTE funding have been initiated in this"
        "college for the benefit of students, faculties and development of this region as well as for"
        "the society at large. The Entrepreneurship Cell of the college having faculties and students"
        "as members, has been awarded national championship thrice in a row between 2008 to 2015 and "
        "for the following years it has come as runners up.The professional involvement of students "
        "in Robotics by working models preparation reflect the height of knowledge and application "
        "of the students.They have won top positions at various inter-college meets in the State as "
        "well as national level technological competitions and at cultural meets.\n\n"

        "With a student strength of three thousand at BCET, our efforts are directed to accommodate "
        "and address the expections of every student by the way of enabling them to participate in "
        "seminars,workshops in and out of the Institute, apart from educational tours and industrial"
        "project works. To refine the necessary attitude, aptitude and skills to achieve placement "
        "on corporate sector, the Institute is supportive to the students by arranging periodical "
        "tests and group interaction exercises. We endeavour to equip our students with both technical "
        "and management skills, so that they may contribute to the industry being excellent professionals.\n\n"

        "We are determined to retain this level of superiority already in command and improve further"
        "in every sphere of academic activities including research orientation and overall development"
        "of the students at BCET .\n\n"

        </string>
    <string name="large_text4">
        "Prof. (Dr.) Alok Kumar Bharadwaj\n"
                  "Principal\n"
        "Bengal College of Engineering and Technology\n\n"

    </string>
    <string name="large_text5">
        "Prof. (Dr.) A.C. Ganguli\n"
            "Director (Admin)\n"
     "SKS Educational and Social Trust\n\n"

        </string>
    <string name="large_text6">
           "Shri. S K Sharma\n"
              "Chairman\n"
"Bengal College of Engineering and Technology\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_course">CourseActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>


</resources>
